const quizQuestions = [
    // Question #1
    {
        question: "What does HTML stands for?",
        optionA: "Hyper Text Modular Linguistics",
        optionB: "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
        optionC: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        optionD: "Hyper Transport Marketing Language",
        correctAnswer: "optionC"
    },

    // Question #2
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        optionA: "Cascading Style Sheets",
        optionB: "Cascading Stun Sheets",
        optionC: "Colorful Style Sheets",
        optionD: "Cascading Style Startups",
        correctAnswer: "optionA"
    },

    // Question #3
    {
        question: "What color is #FFFFFF?",
        optionA: "Blue",
        optionB: "Black",
        optionC: "White",
        optionD: "Purple",
        correctAnswer: "optionC"
    },

    // Question #4
    {
        question: "What are different types of lists in HTML?",
        optionA: "Ordered and Unordered Lists",
        optionB: "Dotted and Dashed Lists",
        optionC: "Bolded and Underlined Lists",
        optionD: "Numbered and Bullet Lists",
        correctAnswer: "optionA"
    },

    // Question #5
    {
        question: "Which is not considered a formatting tag in HTML?",
        optionA: "<b>",
        optionB: "<a>",
        optionC: "<i>",
        optionD: "<sub>",
        correctAnswer: "optionB"
    },

    // Question #6
    {
        question: "What kind of color is #000000",
        optionA: "Hex",
        optionB: "RGB",
        optionC: "HSL",
        optionD: "Binary",
        correctAnswer: "optionA"
    },

    // Question #7
    {
        question: "How is JavaScript called?",
        optionA: "<nav>",
        optionB: "<html>",
        optionC: "<script>",
        optionD: "<style>",
        correctAnswer: "optionC"
    },

    // Question #8
    {
        question: "How is a tag ended?",
        optionA: "</>",
        optionB: "<>",
        optionC: "<,>",
        optionD: "<->",
        correctAnswer: "optionA"
    },

    // Question #9
    {
        question: "How is JavaScript called?",
        optionA: "<nav>",
        optionB: "<html>",
        optionC: "<script>",
        optionD: "<style>",
        correctAnswer: "optionC"
    },

    // Question #10
    {
        question: "How is a tag ended?",
        optionA: "</>",
        optionB: "<>",
        optionC: "<,>",
        optionD: "<->",
        correctAnswer: "optionA"
    }

];
